<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebLogic Image Tool</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/index.html</link>
    <description>WebLogic Image Tool Oracle is finding ways for organizations using WebLogic Server to run important workloads, to move those workloads into the cloud, and to simplify and speed up the application deployment life cycle. By adopting industry standards, such as Docker and Kubernetes, WebLogic now runs in a cloud neutral infrastructure. To help simplify and automate the creation of container images for WebLogic Server, we are providing this open source WebLogic Image Tool (WIT).</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start Guide</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/quickstart/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/quickstart/index.html</guid>
      <description>Use this Quick Start guide to create a Linux based WebLogic container image.&#xA;StepsBefore you begin Make sure that you have fulfilled the Prerequisites and Setup requirements. Overview The high level steps for creating an image are: Download the Java and WebLogic installers from the Oracle Software Delivery Cloud . Add the installers to the cache store. Run the imagetool command to create the image. Do this Download these Java and WebLogic installers from the Oracle Software Delivery Cloud and save them in a directory of your choice, for example, /home/acmeuser/wls-installers:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Guide</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/index.html</guid>
      <description>The User Guide provides detailed usage information for the WebLogic Image Tool, including typical use case scenarios.&#xA;PrerequisitesLearn about the Image Tool&#39;s prerequisites.&#xA;SetupInstall the WebLogic Image Tool.&#xA;Image Tool CommandsLearn about the commands supported by the Image Tool.&#xA;CleanupLearn how to clean up temporary directories created by the Image Tool.&#xA;ConfigurationLearn about advanced configuration of the Image Tool.&#xA;LoggingLearn how to configure the Image Tool logging framework.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samples</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/samples/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/samples/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create an image with full Internet accessSample that creates an image with full Internet access.&#xA;Create an image without Internet accessSample that creates an image without Internet access.&#xA;Patch an existing imageSample that patches an existing image.&#xA;Create an image with a WLS domain using WDTSample that creates an image containing a WLS domain using WDT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Guide</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/developer/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/developer/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Developer Guide provides information for developers who want to build the installer from source or contribute to the code.&#xA;Build from sourceHow to build the Image Tool from source.&#xA;Contribute to WITHow to contribute to the development of the Image Tool.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>