<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>User Guide on WebLogic Image Tool</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in User Guide on WebLogic Image Tool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/prerequisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/prerequisites/</guid>
      <description>Docker client and daemon on the build machine, with minimum Docker version 18.03.1.ce. OPTIONALLY: Podman 3.x may be used in place of Docker. Installers for WebLogic Server and JDK from the Oracle Software Delivery Cloud. When using any of the patching options, --patches, --recommendedPatches, or --latestPSU, you will need to provide Oracle Support credentials. When using the imagetool alias from setup.sh instead of the shell script (imagetool.sh), Bash version 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/setup/</guid>
      <description> Download and unzip the release ZIP file to a desired location. OPTIONALLY: You may build the project (mvn clean package) to create the ZIP installer in ./imagetool/target. Set the JAVA_HOME environment variable to the location of the Java install (see Prerequisites).  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleanup</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/cleanup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/cleanup/</guid>
      <description>The Image Tool creates a temporary Docker context directory, prefixed by wlsimgbuilder_temp, every time the tool runs. Under normal circumstances, this context directory will be deleted. However, if the process is aborted or the tool is unable to remove the directory, it is safe for you to delete it manually.
By default, the Image Tool creates the Docker context directory under the user&amp;rsquo;s home directory. If you prefer to use a different directory for the temporary context, set the environment variable WLSIMG_BLDDIR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:19:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/logging/</guid>
      <description>The Image Tool uses standard Java logging. To alter the default logging settings, you can modify the logging.properties file under the bin directory where you installed the Image Tool.
To enable debug logging In logging.properties, comment the existing handlers property and uncomment the second handlers line below the first line that you just commented. This should make the logging.properties file look something like this:
#handlers=java.util.logging.ConsoleHandler handlers=java.util.logging.FileHandler, java.util.logging.ConsoleHandler Then, change level to FINE or FINER.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
