<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Image Tool on WebLogic Image Tool</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Image Tool on WebLogic Image Tool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create Image</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/create-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/create-image/</guid>
      <description>The create command helps build a WebLogic container image from a given base OS image. There are a number of optional parameters for this feature. The required option for the command is marked.
NOTE: The WebLogic Image Tool does not support a Stack Patch Bundle (SPB; see Doc ID 2764636.1), because an SPB is not a patch but a mechanism for applying all PSU and recommended CPU and SPU patches to a WebLogic Server installation, similar to invoking the Image Tool create command with the --recommendedPatches option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Auxiliary Image</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/create-aux-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/create-aux-image/</guid>
      <description>The createAuxImage command helps build a container image from a given base OS image. Auxiliary images are very small images providing the WDT install files with WDT models, archives, and variables for WebLogic Kubernetes Operator - Auxiliary Images. These images are an alternative approach for including Model-in-Image model files, application archive files, WebLogic Deploying Tooling installation files, or other types of files, in your WebLogic Server Kubernetes Operator environment.
There are a number of optional parameters for this feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebase Image</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/rebase-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/rebase-image/</guid>
      <description>The rebase command creates a new container image and copies an existing WebLogic domain to that new image.
The new container image can be based on an existing image in the repository or created as part of the rebase operation similar to the create command.
Usage: imagetool rebase [OPTIONS]    Parameter Definition Default     --sourceImage (Required) Source Image containing the WebLogic domain.    --tag (Required) Tag for the final build image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Image</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/update-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/update-image/</guid>
      <description>After you have created a container image with the Image Tool, you may want to change it from time to time. Use the update command to update the existing container images created with the Image Tool. For example, you may want to:
 Apply a WebLogic patch Apply the latest PSU from Oracle Create a new WebLogic domain (if one did not already exist) Deploy a new application to an existing domain Modify the domain configuration (add a data source, change a port number, and such)  NOTE: The WebLogic Image Tool does not support a Stack Patch Bundle (SPB; see Doc ID 2764636.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspect Image</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/inspect-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/inspect-image/</guid>
      <description>The inspect command reports on the contents of a container image providing version and location information for Java and WebLogic installations.
Usage: imagetool inspect [OPTIONS]    Parameter Definition Default     --image, -i (Required) The image ID or image name to be inspected.    --builder, -b Executable to process the Dockerfile. Use the full path of the executable if not on your path. docker   --format The output format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cache</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/cache/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-image-tool/userguide/tools/cache/</guid>
      <description>The Image Tool maintains a local file cache store. This store is used to look up where the Java, WebLogic Server installers, and WebLogic Server patches reside in the local file system.
By default, the cache store is located in the user&amp;rsquo;s $HOME/cache directory. Under this directory, the lookup information is stored in the .metadata file. All automatically downloaded patches also reside in this directory.
You can change the default cache store location by setting the environment variable WLSIMG_CACHEDIR:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
